[
  {
    "category": "Aircraft",
    "id": "aircraft",
    "content": [
      {
        "question": "Can I charter a helicopter along with a jet?",
        "id": "c_01jexCKHA92DX5hnvw3sD62m84",
        "answer": "<p>Yes, JetLevel Aviation offers the flexibility to charter both a private jet and a helicopter. This service is ideal for seamless travel, allowing you to connect to remote locations or avoid ground traffic. Our team will coordinate the helicopter charter to align with your jet schedule, ensuring a smooth and efficient travel experience.</p>"
      },
      {
        "question": "Are private jets safe?",
        "id": "c_01jGs2kC4k7DN1M9dNJQ5VQq9E",
        "answer": "<p>Yes, private jets are highly safe, adhering to stringent safety standards set by aviation authorities. Operators follow rigorous maintenance schedules, and pilots undergo extensive training and certifications. Additionally, private jet travel often reduces exposure to crowded airports, adding a layer of safety and convenience. JetLevel Aviation prioritizes passenger safety, working with certified operators and experienced crews to ensure secure and reliable flights.</p>"
      },
      {
        "question": "Are two pilots used on all flights?",
        "id": "c_01jgS63w99731ze3c6T960wSP8",
        "answer": "<p>Yes, all our private jet flights use <strong>two highly trained pilots</strong> for enhanced safety and compliance with FAA regulations. Both pilots hold <strong>ATP (Airline Transport Pilot) licenses</strong> and undergo regular training and proficiency checks to ensure they meet the highest industry standards. This ensures optimal safety and operational efficiency on every flight.</p>"
      },
      {
        "question": "Can I bring Oxygen on a Private Jet?",
        "id": "c_01jgs690hwXMDZNhR2d18YR3w8",
        "answer": "<p>Yes, you can bring oxygen on a private jet, but it requires prior coordination. Inform us in advance so we can ensure compliance with safety regulations and confirm the aircraft is equipped to accommodate your needs. Some private jets can provide onboard oxygen systems for medical requirements, offering a safe and comfortable flight experience.</p>"
      },
      {
        "question": "Can I take golf clubs with me on the private jet?",
        "id": "c_01jgs65MM1pc47nFr0Sy4BP0AY",
        "answer": "<p>Yes, you can bring golf clubs on a private jet. Private jets typically have sufficient luggage space for golf bags. For larger groups or multiple bags, let us know in advance to ensure the selected aircraft accommodates your needs. Traveling privately ensures your clubs are handled with care and arrive safely.</p>"
      },
      {
        "question": "Can I take golf clubs with me on the private jet?",
        "id": "c_01JGs64j2kPk1D61EyAH18rAkc",
        "answer": "<p>Yes, all our private jet flights use <strong>two highly trained pilots</strong> for enhanced safety and compliance with FAA regulations. Both pilots hold <strong>ATP (Airline Transport Pilot) licenses</strong> and undergo regular training and proficiency checks to ensure they meet the highest industry standards. This ensures optimal safety and operational efficiency on every flight.</p>"
      },
      {
        "question": "Can I take a wheelchair on a private jet?",
        "id": "c_01JGS66HWW1p3ab60CGG59bZKX",
        "answer": "<p>Yes, you can bring a wheelchair on a private jet. Most private jets can accommodate wheelchairs, and our team ensures a smooth boarding process, including assistance with mobility and securely stowing the wheelchair. For powered or oversized wheelchairs, please inform us in advance to confirm compatibility with the aircraft and arrange necessary accommodations.</p>"
      },
      {
        "question": "How far can a private jet fly?",
        "id": "c_01JGs61ZK898v066vWva2STJzT",
        "answer": "<p>The range of a private jet varies by model, with most capable of flying <strong>1,500 to 7,500 miles</strong> on a single tank. Light jets typically cover <strong>1,500-2,500 miles</strong>, ideal for regional trips. Midsize jets range from <strong>2,000-4,000 miles</strong>, while large jets and ultra-long-range jets, like the Gulfstream G650, can fly up to <strong>7,500 miles</strong>, enabling non-stop international travel.</p>"
      },
      {
        "question": "How fast do private jets fly?",
        "id": "c_01jgS5y6rY43KrgAZJ3ddxrGef",
        "answer": "<p>Private jets typically fly at speeds ranging from <strong>400 to 700 miles per hour (mph)</strong>, depending on the model and altitude. Light jets average around <strong>400-450 mph</strong>, while larger jets like the Gulfstream G650 can reach speeds of up to <strong>700 mph</strong>. Their efficiency at higher altitudes (35,000-45,000 feet) allows for faster travel compared to commercial airliners.</p>"
      },
      {
        "question": "Can I take skis or snowboards on a private jet?",
        "id": "c_01Jgs67Gp5zft44Rzen0qnAfk4",
        "answer": "<p>Yes, you can bring skis or snowboards on a private jet. Most private jets have ample luggage space to accommodate ski equipment. For larger groups or multiple items, let us know in advance to ensure the selected aircraft meets your storage needs. Private jet travel ensures your gear is securely transported and easily accessible for your winter adventure.</p>"
      },
      {
        "question": "How many pilots does JetLevel require?",
        "id": "c_01jGs6Bhy0MPc2dbz3AcY5VtnP",
        "answer": "<p>JetLevel requires <strong>two pilots</strong> on all flights to ensure maximum safety and compliance with FAA regulations. Both pilots are highly experienced, holding <strong>ATP (Airline Transport Pilot) licenses</strong> and undergoing regular training and proficiency checks. This dual-pilot approach ensures the highest levels of safety and operational excellence on every flight.</p>"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is ARG/US?",
        "id": "c_01Jgs6CFddyrd0nXd5FR2vGajS",
        "answer": "<p>ARG/US (Aviation Research Group/United States) is a respected aviation safety organization that provides <strong>safety ratings, audits, and certification for charter operators</strong>. Their ratings—Gold, Gold Plus, and Platinum—are based on rigorous evaluations of operator practices, pilot qualifications, maintenance standards, and operational history. Choosing an ARG/US-rated operator ensures a commitment to the highest safety and operational standards in private aviation.</p>"
      },
      {
        "question": "How will I know what type of Aircraft to book for my flight?",
        "id": "c_01jGS6864CebyF52W15d5H7dnP",
        "answer": "<p>Our team will assist you in selecting the ideal aircraft based on your travel needs, including <strong>distance, passenger count, luggage requirements, and preferences</strong>. We’ll provide tailored recommendations, detailing each aircraft's capacity, range, and amenities, ensuring a comfortable and efficient flight. Whether it’s a light jet for short trips or a long-range jet for international travel, we ensure the perfect fit for your journey.</p>"
      },
      {
        "question": "What safety standards do your private jets, pilots, and crew abide by?",
        "id": "c_01jgs630Zc294MFNTM90GS5ww2",
        "answer": "<p>Our private jets, pilots, and crew adhere to the <strong>highest safety standards</strong>, including FAA Part 135 regulations for charter operations. Jets undergo regular maintenance and inspections by certified professionals. Pilots meet strict qualifications, holding <strong>ATP licenses</strong> and extensive flight experience. We also follow <strong>ARGUS and Wyvern safety audits</strong> and conduct rigorous training for our crew to ensure exceptional safety and service.</p>"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Charter",
    "id": "charter",
    "content": [
      {
        "question": "Can I choose my flight departure time?",
        "id": "c_01JgS404ZrQzmnH6rFm3X69GEB",
        "answer": "<p>Yes, with JetLevel Aviation, you have the flexibility to choose your flight departure time. Private jet charters operate on your schedule, allowing you to tailor your travel plans to your needs. Our team ensures a seamless experience, providing convenience and control over your itinerary.</p>"
      },
      {
        "question": "Can I book by the seat or share a private plane with another party?",
        "id": "c_01jGvrWk7vDYv019Y70AXS6y8x",
        "answer": "<p>JetLevel Aviation specializes in full private jet charters, meaning you book the entire aircraft for your exclusive use. We do not typically offer by-the-seat booking or shared flights. This ensures privacy, flexibility, and a personalized travel experience tailored to your needs.</p>"
      },
      {
        "question": "Can I change the schedule or the itinerary of my flight?",
        "id": "c_01JGVRTvBeVB35n02w8M3s36R9",
        "answer": "<p>Yes, private jet charters with JetLevel Aviation offer flexibility to adjust your schedule or itinerary. Changes can often be accommodated, subject to aircraft availability and operational requirements. Our team works closely with you to ensure your travel needs are met seamlessly.</p>"
      },
      {
        "question": "Can I fly to multiple destinations on the same day?",
        "id": "c_01JgvRPBq9fBdh7J0mE9mkRbKk",
        "answer": "<p>Yes, with JetLevel Aviation, you can fly to multiple destinations on the same day. Private jet charters offer flexibility to customize your itinerary, allowing for efficient travel between locations without the delays of commercial flights. Our team ensures seamless coordination for a hassle-free experience.</p>"
      },
      {
        "question": "Can I make last-minute changes to my flight itinerary?",
        "id": "c_01jgvrXT16y4GN0HXkrGmK9613",
        "answer": "<p>Yes, JetLevel Aviation allows last-minute changes to your flight itinerary, subject to aircraft availability and operational considerations. Our team works diligently to accommodate adjustments and ensure a smooth, flexible travel experience.</p>"
      },
      {
        "question": "Can I travel with my pet?",
        "id": "c_01JgVrT58q5nBC58m4CPg06ty9",
        "answer": "<p>Yes, you can travel with your pet on a private jet charter. JetLevel Aviation welcomes pets and ensures their comfort and safety during the flight. Let us know your pet’s needs in advance, and we’ll arrange a pet-friendly experience tailored to you.</p>"
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of Private Jet Charter Service do you offer at JetLevel Aviation?",
        "id": "c_01JGvrw3fZ4pAB6Abb5NY1vJF9",
        "answer": "<p>JetLevel Aviation offers a range of private jet charter services, including <strong>on-demand charters</strong>, <strong>group charters</strong>, <strong>corporate travel</strong>, <strong>luxury leisure trips</strong>, and <strong>medical or emergency flights</strong>. We tailor each service to your unique needs, providing access to a global fleet of aircraft for a seamless and personalized travel experience.</p>"
      },
      {
        "question": "Is it possible to add a last-minute passenger on my flight?",
        "id": "c_01JgvRVc4BW6QD66fM1nTV351C",
        "answer": "<p>Yes, adding a last-minute passenger to your private jet flight is usually possible, provided the aircraft's seating capacity and weight limits allow it. Notify JetLevel Aviation as soon as possible, and we'll make the necessary arrangements to accommodate the additional traveler.</p>"
      },
      {
        "question": "How far in advance do I need to book my Charter Flight?",
        "id": "c_01Jgvrx7C4t2gRCST5kc8YT365",
        "answer": "<p>You can book a charter flight with JetLevel Aviation as little as <strong>a few hours in advance</strong>, depending on aircraft availability and logistics. However, booking <strong>24-48 hours in advance</strong> is recommended to ensure optimal aircraft options and a seamless travel experience.</p>"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Service",
    "id": "service",
    "content": [
      {
        "question": "Can I take golf clubs with me on the private jet?",
        "id": "c_01jgs478QmsrEWq98C4F30r2x6",
        "answer": "<p>Yes, you can bring golf clubs on a private jet. Private jets offer ample luggage space, and our team ensures your equipment is safely accommodated. Let us know your requirements, and we'll match you with an aircraft that meets your needs for a hassle-free golf trip.</p>"
      },
      {
        "question": "Can I take a wheelchair on a private jet?",
        "id": "c_01JGvs3C8nGr676Vdb53EAf98S",
        "answer": "<p>Yes, wheelchairs can be accommodated on private jets. JetLevel Aviation ensures accessibility and can arrange for aircraft with suitable space and amenities. Let us know your requirements, and we'll coordinate the necessary arrangements for a comfortable travel experience.</p>"
      },
      {
        "question": "Can I take skis or snowboards on a private jet?",
        "id": "c_01JgVS3yM3Py23bFmHAtSh5hhJ",
        "answer": "<p>Yes, you can bring skis or snowboards on a private jet. JetLevel Aviation ensures your equipment is safely stored, and we’ll match you with an aircraft that accommodates your luggage needs. Notify us in advance for a seamless experience.</p>"
      },
      {
        "question": "Is smoking allowed on private jets?",
        "id": "c_01JGVS4W3b512qg786Sv1nKgSB",
        "answer": "<p>Smoking policies on private jets vary by operator and aircraft. Some jets allow smoking, while others prohibit it due to regulations or preferences. Let JetLevel Aviation know your preferences, and we’ll match you with an appropriate aircraft if smoking is permitted.</p>"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Broker",
    "id": "broker",
    "content": [
      {
        "question": "Can you arrange ground transportation?",
        "id": "c_01jgs3YVZWVybrE2wv9JkQZN4s",
        "answer": "<p>Yes, JetLevel Aviation can arrange ground transportation for your journey. Whether you need a luxury car, SUV, or limousine, we coordinate with trusted providers to ensure a seamless transfer to and from the airport. Our team tailors arrangements to your preferences for a convenient and stress-free experience.</p>"
      },
      {
        "question": "Why should I book with JetLevel?",
        "id": "c_01jGVRnNZ70AzD6b04H7vTWrBz",
        "answer": "<p>Booking with JetLevel Aviation ensures a premium travel experience with personalized service, 24/7 support, and access to a global network of top-tier aircraft. We prioritize safety, transparency, and efficiency, tailoring every flight to your needs for seamless, stress-free travel.</p>"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Airport",
    "id": "airport",
    "content": [
      {
        "question": "How long should I arrive before departure?",
        "id": "c_01JgS3Y95h8tm8084hHNkv2Qje",
        "answer": "<p>For private jet flights, arriving 15-30 minutes before departure is typically sufficient. Unlike commercial flights, private jet travel offers streamlined security and check-in processes, minimizing wait times. JetLevel Aviation ensures a hassle-free experience, allowing you to board quickly and depart on your schedule.</p>"
      },
      {
        "question": "Can I travel to secondary or underserved airports?",
        "id": "c_01JGs6p5rekD7Kf2QyfdqCR639",
        "answer": "<p>Yes, private jets can access <strong>secondary and underserved airports</strong>, providing unparalleled flexibility. With the ability to land on shorter runways and at smaller airports, private jets bring you closer to your destination, often bypassing crowded major hubs. This allows for efficient and convenient travel to remote or less-serviced locations.</p>"
      },
      {
        "question": "Is there parking at the FBO or the business aviation terminal?",
        "id": "c_01JGs6kgJ7FWByMdjamyN956cg",
        "answer": "<p>Yes, most FBOs (Fixed Base Operators) or business aviation terminals offer <strong>parking facilities</strong> for passengers. Many provide convenient, secure parking options, including valet services, for your vehicle while you travel. Contact your chosen FBO in advance to confirm parking availability and any associated fees or services.</p>"
      },
      {
        "question": "How long in advance do I need to show up at the airport if I book a Private Charter?",
        "id": "c_01JGvrk8nh4HpTHar5Xp6QK9N2",
        "answer": "<p>For a private charter, you only need to arrive <strong>15-30 minutes before departure</strong>. The streamlined check-in process and private terminals eliminate long waits, providing a quick and hassle-free experience tailored to your schedule.</p>"
      },
      {
        "question": "How does customs and immigration work when flying Internationally on a Private Jet?",
        "id": "c_01jGvRkw6JgWG3GC5dAda6VwnK",
        "answer": "<p>When flying internationally on a private jet, customs and immigration are expedited through private terminals or FBOs (Fixed Base Operators). Passengers typically present passports to customs officers on-site, with minimal wait times and personalized service. JetLevel Aviation ensures all necessary documentation and clearances are prearranged for a smooth and efficient process.</p>"
      },
      {
        "question": "Do I still need my passport when flying on a Private Jet Internationally?",
        "id": "c_01JGVrmgTPyS74vyfgfFTemBqC",
        "answer": "<p>Yes, a passport is required when flying internationally on a private jet. Customs and immigration regulations still apply, and your passport must be valid for the destination's entry requirements. JetLevel Aviation ensures a smooth process by coordinating all necessary documentation.</p>"
      },
      {
        "question": "Do I have to go through boarding formalities?",
        "id": "c_01jGS6n7HhgBq50AA53q6KGrAV",
        "answer": "<p>Private jet travel significantly minimizes boarding formalities. Passengers typically bypass standard airport security lines, completing quick identity and baggage checks at the <strong>FBO (Fixed Base Operator)</strong>. This streamlined process ensures a hassle-free and efficient boarding experience, allowing you to arrive just minutes before departure.</p>"
      },
      {
        "question": "Where do I meet the aircraft?",
        "id": "c_01JGs6Q3K4TSVGPJVsTWmcjDe5",
        "answer": "<p>You’ll meet the aircraft at the <strong>Fixed Base Operator (FBO)</strong> or private aviation terminal at your departure airport. The FBO provides a dedicated and convenient facility for private jet passengers. Upon arrival, our team or the FBO staff will guide you directly to your aircraft for a seamless boarding experience. Specific details will be shared before your flight.</p>"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Price",
    "id": "price",
    "content": [
      {
        "question": "How much is a private jet per hour?",
        "id": "c_01jgS40SpqTA4nGz0W5VZE6Dxj",
        "answer": "<p>The cost of a private jet per hour typically ranges from <strong>$1,800 to $10,000</strong>, depending on the jet type. Light jets are on the lower end, while midsize, heavy, or ultra-long-range jets are higher. Additional factors like route, airport fees, and onboard services may affect pricing. JetLevel Aviation provides transparent quotes tailored to your travel needs.</p>"
      },
      {
        "question": "Are there extra costs per passenger when flying private?",
        "id": "c_01JGVs2EcFd21Z72FTcaqe5VC8",
        "answer": "<p>No, private jet charter pricing is generally based on the aircraft, not the number of passengers. However, additional costs could arise for services like catering, luggage exceeding weight limits, or landing fees at specific airports. JetLevel Aviation provides transparent quotes, ensuring no surprises.</p>"
      },
      {
        "question": "Is catering included in the quote?",
        "id": "c_01JGvryM6Wp7scsF5Y8YrmRm1C",
        "answer": "<p>Yes, standard catering is typically included in JetLevel Aviation's private jet charter quotes. Custom or premium catering requests can also be arranged for an additional cost, tailored to your preferences. Let us know your needs, and we’ll ensure an exceptional in-flight dining experience.</p>"
      },
      {
        "question": "Is deicing included in the quote?",
        "id": "c_01JGVs18C15wf5EbM71AvefyNy",
        "answer": "<p>Deicing is typically <strong>not included</strong> in the initial charter quote, as it is a variable cost dependent on weather conditions and airport requirements. If deicing is necessary, the cost will be billed separately. JetLevel Aviation provides transparent pricing and keeps you informed of any additional charges.</p>"
      },
      {
        "question": "Is food included in the price of the charter?",
        "id": "c_01JgVS1x2e78Vybj6z73m6c844",
        "answer": "<p>Yes, standard in-flight catering is typically included in the price of a private jet charter with JetLevel Aviation. For specific or premium dining requests, additional charges may apply. Let us know your preferences, and we’ll tailor the catering to enhance your travel experience.</p>"
      }
    ]
  }
]